Ishan Bidaye

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACT

+91 84118 72328/+91 89562 23281

ishan0110@gmail.com

nune, Maharashtra, India

in Ishan Bidaye

ABOUT ME

I specialize in crafting captivating social media graphics, designing sleek websites, and creating eye-catching print materials. My goal is to go above and beyond expectations, ensuring that the designs I create leave a lasting impression. Let's work together to transform your ideas into visually stunning realities.

EDUCATION

2019-2021

International School of Design, Pune M.Des Graphic Design

2018-2019

Fergusson College, Pune

Certification in Digital Photography

2014-2017

Fergusson College, Pune

BSc Environmental Science

SKILLS

- Graphic design
- UI Design
- Motion graphics and animations
- Professional Photography
- Figma

EXPERIENCE

Amura Marketing Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Senior Visualizer | 2023 - Current

Work on multi-disciplinary platforms including print and digital mediums for advertising and branding on client brands.

- Designing engaging social media posts
- Branding and identity for new or existing brands throughout the country
- · Guiding junior designers on day to day basis

Schbang Digital Solutions Pvt. Ltd. Senior Visualizer | 2022-2023

Discussed project ideas and goals with each account manager and turned these visions into real visual designs that meet the need using illustrations, artwork, design elements, and fonts. Create original rich images for company clients.

 Creating social media designs for high end clients including Amazon, Domino's, Brigade group and many more.

BeyondWalls Visualizer | 2021-2022

Real estate marketing and branding company based in Pune. My job role included creating premium, high end designs for digital and print campaigns and social media pages.

- Creating stunning visuals for campaigns
- Social media posts and simple animations for reels and videos
- Brochures, standees and hoarding ads designs

Zest Creative Junior Graphic Designer | 2020-2021

Got to work on numerous brands from the tech, pharma, lifestyle, FMCG and real estate industries. Hands-on practical learning experience of softwares and tools under the guidance of qualified seniors and leaders.

Social media posts and simple animations for reels and videos